jihosoft.com 2017-11-20

# Jihosoft Customer Privacy Policy

Jihosoft’s Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Jihosoft anytime you interact with Jihosoft, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Jihosoft products and services, or when you contact our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Jihosoft, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

### Personal Information

We will ask for the personal information when you register for certain services.  
The information we collect may be combined with the information from our services and other companies.  
The cookies and other technologies are used to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience.

### Uses of Information

We will inform you of other products or services offered by Jihosoft Studio.  
We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. We can guarantee it.

### Your Choices

When we collect information from you, you may tell us that you do not want it in the future and we will respect your wishes.  
You may also turn off cookies in your browser.

### Information Security and Quality

We intend to protect your personal information and maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting certain sensitive information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality.

### Anti-malware statement

Jihosoft STRONGLY OPPPOSES all forms of malware. Jihosoft applications will never intentionally jeopardize our customers’ privacy or security. All applications are designed to be easily removable from the computer through an uninstall utility. Jihosoft does not employ the use of reinstallers and avoids all features that may be found in any type of malware. No Jihosoft application is designed to collect any personally identifiable information from any user. Jihosoft applications do not contain, nor are they bundled with, any third party applications (spyware, adware, malware, etc.) that would jeopardize our customers’ security or their privacy. All Jihosoft applications pass both Kaspersky and Rising vigorous anti-virus/malware tests before public release.
